(Shayla) Did you have something
to do with Vera getting busted?
Who told you to put your business
- anywhere near social media?
- My aspirational little brother.
Someone's gonna get hurt for this.
- (Elliot) What happened to Angela?
- She's not gonna work out for us.
Not on this level.
You didn't have to
stick up for me in there.
Don't do it again.
Evil Corp tapped you for CTO, yes?
- You're ruining your life.
- I also ruined yours.
Terry Colby was involved in the cover up
of the Washington Township
toxic waste scandal.
Sharon, how do you not blow
your brains out, married to him?
I'm in here.
Do you mind sleeping here tonight?
That girl in there is mine.
If you're around tonight,
come over and tell me about it.
[phone ringing]
[dog barking]
Shayla?
(Vera on phone) Sometimes
the universe aligns perfectly.
Here I am, locked away,
still it brings you right to me.
[Nancy Sinatra and Lee Hazelwood's
Some Velvet Morning]
♪ ♪
(Elliot voice-over) I feel the sensation.
Fight or flight.
It's constant.
I should just pick one.
I, Elliot Alderson, am flight.
I am fear.
I am anxiety, terror, panic.
♪ Some velvet morning
when I'm straight ♪
Synced and corrected by skoad
Resync by GoldenBeard
♪ I'm gonna open up your gate ♪
♪ ♪
Doesn't feel real.
- You should eat.
- Not hungry.
I don't know what I ordered.
I'm sorry.
- You don't like the guisado?
- No, it's good.
Thank you.
- What are you thinking about?
- First time we met.
Doesn't feel that long ago.
Now look at us.
Who would have thought?
- If I could go back and undo this...
- You can't.
You promised me.
I'm gonna get you out of this, okay?
Time's up.
Let's go.
Elliot!
Sit down. Sit down.
[door shuts]
(DJ) Come with me.
Let's go.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
- Hello?
- The origin of your name.
(Vera) I looked it up for you, bruh.
- Where are you taking her?
- (Vera) Elliot.
"Brave and true."
Did you know the origin of
"brave" evolved from "savage?
I don't know what this is about,
but you need to let her go.
(Vera) You know, funny thing.
My name means something similar.
Brave traveler.
Adventurer.
Savage traveler becomes brave traveler.
Are we savages, or are we brave?
Don't know, bro.
Listen to me, man.
When I found out you did
this, I didn't get angry.
I got impressed.
Your power.
I want it, Elliot.
And I want it so bad it makes my dick hard.
And I want it today.
I don't know what you think I can do.
I can't just hack you out of prison.
Not all prisons are networked,
and even if yours is,
it would take weeks to find security holes.
Has to be tonight.
I got crosshairs on my heart.
I don't make it out,
I'm dead, and that ain't
meant to be just yet.
You do your thing, bro.
You're asking the impossible.
When we cross paths tonight,
Elliot, I'ma hug you.
Please listen, man.
Shayla... this is on me.
Okay?
You got to let her go.
Oh, that?
She cool, bro.
Trust me, she cool.
She'll be there tonight too.
It'll be one big happy happy.
[laughs]
Hey, Elliot.
I love you, bro.
[dial tone]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[peeling tires]
- Where's Shayla?
- Man, I'm not gonna tell you again.
Stop asking so many questions.
Come on.
(Elliot voice-over) Vera
may be out of his mind,
but yes, it is possible to
hack into a prison's network.
Most of them use regular
industrial control systems.
[keys drop]
I'm a blind man to what
Vera sees in this dude.
Amen. Techie computer hacker
genius, my thick Dominican dick.
[chuckles]
(Elliot voice-over) When
you have control of that,
you basically have
control of the cell doors.
[Flipper yips]
But what these morons don't know is,
it's almost impossible
without any research.
Time to shine your cojones and get to work.
Our only rule: do what we say.
You violate that dictate,
we kill your sweetheart.
Yo, Isaac.
- How my dic-Tate?
- Shut up, bitch.
[laughs] Dictate.
[stirring music]
♪ ♪
(Elliot voice-over) Vera's bro, Isaac.
Something about him bugs me,
and you know what I like
to do when that happens?
♪ ♪
_
Hi, I'm trying to reach Mr. Beckett.
When would Mr. Lattimer be available?
I can come in today.
I already told you what
it's in reference to.
I'm trying again for Mrs. Nayar.
Regarding the Washington Township scandal.
I may have found some information.
Please don't put me on hold again.
♪ ♪
Happy Monday, Angela.
How fun.
[phone vibrates]
- Thanks.
- Mm-hmm.
[phone vibrates]
(Angela) I'm Emily Moss's daughter.
Angela Moss.
- I called...
- Six times.
Yes.
I'm here to discuss the
Washington Township case.
I'm listening.
You represented the victim's families.
26 families, mine included.
I thought with the latest
news in the data dumps...
the Terry Colby scandal,
his covering up the chemical waste spill.
Alleged.
- Well, and documents.
- Superficial.
But if we bring this
stronger, more concrete case...
you'll see that I have the
evidence from the data dumps.
- Along with further research.
- Stickies.
Oh, and you've highlighted and underlined.
This is serious.
So, you want to take Internet
gossip to federal court
and throw it at the strongest conglomerate
in the history of civilization?
Guy in the suit.
Twice convicted of sexual assault,
charged again this past weekend.
Raped his pregnant girlfriend.
Bashed her head in with an Xbox.
Claims she cheated during Halo.
Yet I have a better
chance of defending him.
You called back.
I called every lawyer from this case,
and you're the only
one that called me back.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[indistinct radio chatter]
_
[man speaking in distance]
Shit. Shit, shit.
(Elliot voice-over) Connection
closed by remote host.
But we had a fish. I was in.
The exploit started to run,
and then... was it the code?
(Isaac) Brah, what's the deal?
[Flipper barks]
I got to take her for a walk.
Why?
'Cause she'll piss on the floor if I don't.
You think I've a shit
about your goddamn floor?
[laughs]
I'm just playing, brah.
Yeah, you can take her.
You hear what I said?
I said you can take her.
Come on.
- It's out.
- Okay, got you.
Did she like my little toy?
- Did you write that exploit yourself?
- I had an hour.
So what, you just pulled code
from rapid nine or some shit?
Since when did you become a script kiddie?
I repeat, I had an hour.
Malware detection must have caught it.
- You fucked me.
- Hey, don't put this on me, okay?
Th is a shit show
and you gave me no time to do it right.
I can run circles around an
ICS given the proper whitepapers
and time.
- Where the hell are you going?
- I have no problem telling
these two douchetools they're
gonna have to sit on their pricks
till we can find a better solution.
- You don't understand. These guys are...
- Assholes?
Yeah, I'm gonna tell them what's up.
That's what's up, girl.
Hmm?
Now, let's go.
So none of those guys called
you back, not even Lattimer?
Pussies.
I bet they didn't even
bother to read the data dumps.
But you read them.
You know it took me eight years
to rebuild my career after
our case was dismissed?
So, as much as I think is
company is evil incarnate...
and trust me, they are...
You know, it's not worth it.
What would it take,
hypothetically...
- What do we need to prove our case?
- Hypothetically, a reliable eye witness...
You know, if you miraculously
find someone on the inside to flip.
Someone who was there
when the decision was may to
falsify chemical waste and tells...
So,
unless you're Facebook friends
with one of those assholes,
this hypothetical is just that.
Let's move on.
Where are you working these?
You have a boyfriend?
How's your dad?
I work for a company
that doesn't respect me,
my boyfriend recently cheated on me,
and my father is drowning in debt.
- I'll see you next time.
- Okay.
(Tyrell) Fluorescent lights are hell, no?
Was there a change in schedule?
I thought I had Spencer next.
These interviews, they're
just a waste of your time.
I mean, you know our regulatory
and IP issues inside out.
I was thinking we play
hooky the rest of the day,
hit the back nine.
- Is that a Vacheron?
- Patek Philippe Tourbillon.
A gift from the Prince of, uh...
- Oh, does it even matter?
- [laughs]
But I'm not blowing off
my remaining interviews.
Look.
I know you think you
were a shoo-in for CTO,
and you're pissed.
Probably wishing I'd fall
into the subway tracks.
So how about you cut the bullshit?
I'm afraid your paranoia has
gotten the best of you, but,
nevertheless, please excuse me.
I'll leave you to review your notes
before Spencer arrives.
Oh, and thank you for dinner.
The entire evening was enchanting.
The food, the wine, the lovely Sharon.
Please tell her I say hello.
Did you enjoy the view?
What?
- Do you think she wouldn't tell me?
- I'm not sure what you're trying...
You want to watch me piss too?
- I've had several glasses of water.
- Scott, a misunderstand...
Happy to pull my dick out
for you, if that's your thing.
- Watching the Knowles family urinate.
- [zipper pulled]
Hell, I could fly my brother in from Miami.
He has the bladder of a small child.
You'd probably bust a nut
watching him take a leak.
I'm not sure what she told
you, but if I were you,
I would tell her to find
more appropriate ways
of managing her imagination.
Tyrell.
I want you to accept a hard truth,
right here, right now, in front of me.
You are not going to be CTO.
I want to see that look
wash over your face.
It's the only way I know
you'll stop playing these
- silly, silly games.
- [laughs softly]
Oh, I am fully aware you're CTO, Scott.
I'm not sure what more I can offer you.
Wait.
Here.
I feel bad.
After all, you got a child on the way.
You need all the help you can get.
In fact,
this would probably pay off
the rest of your mortgage.
Aren't you still in that neat
little two bedroom in Chelsea?
There.
That's the look I was looking for.
- [zipper pulls up]
- [door shuts]
(Elliot voice-over) I keep brute force
thinking, but it's not working.
I need help.
[door buzzing]
- (Angela) Elliot, you in there?
- (Elliot voice-over) Shit.
Why is she here?
[door buzzing]
(Angela) Elliot!
[door buzzes]
Let me in.
Elliot, you in there?
Little blonde bitty.
(Angela) Elliot, hit the buzzer.
[door buzzing]
I know you're in there.
Go.
Shut her up, and get
her the hell out of here.
(Angela) Elliot. Buzzer. Now.
- What about Darlene?
- She stays with us.
And we'll be watching you,
so don't bother trying any
dumb shit, you dumb shit.
[door buzzing]
[stirring music]
Fuck!
♪ ♪
Do you understand why you're angry?
- 'Cause you know I'm right.
-
- _
_
- Hey.
I tried looking for you after
Gideon's the other night.
- Where were you?
- I had to think about things, you know?
We always knew what Evil Corp did.
We didn't have the proof,
but we knew.
We were right about it all along.
In fact, that news report
wasn't a confirmation.
It was a reminder of how angry I am.
You remember Nayar, the lawyer on the case?
- I went to her, Elliot.
- Listen, Angela, now's not...
I have an idea that will change the world.
I know it sounds really stupid,
but I know how to do it.
- I think it could actually work.
- [stirring music]
- I can't tell you what it is, because...
- (Elliot voice-over) Evil Corp, Angela,
Vera, his brother, Darlene, Shayla.
This is too much.
I should just tell her
what she wants to hear.
Angela,
trust yourself.
You'll do what's right.
♪ ♪
That's all I needed.
- How's Shayla, by the way?
- She's...
- you know.
- Tell her I say hi.
♪ ♪
have no time to pull off
- whatever it is you think you're doing.
- What are you doing here?
- How did you know?
- Darlene.
These guys aren't playing around.
They will fucking kill you.
- Now wise up, and let's go.
- Darlene's in there. We can't leave.
Okay, then we call the cops.
There's no other choice here.
- It's the only way out of this.
- I can't call the cops.
- Shayla will die.
- Oh, come on.
She knew exactly what she
was getting herself into.
You think his employees
have a long life expectancy?
She was dead the minute
- she started working with that maniac.
- Forget it. It's not happening.
(Mr. Robot) This is a zero-sum game.
Calculate all the outcomes.
If you don't pull off
this ridiculous miracle...
and odds are, you won't...
you die, and so does Shayla.
That much we know.
But assume for a second
that you do pull this off,
bust Vera out of prison.
Who's to say he doesn't
kill you, Shayla, Darlene?
It would be in his own
best interest to do that.
Either way, you all end up dead.
It's the only way Vera wins.
Zero-sum, Elliot.
You're playing a game you already lost.
- You know I'm right.
- There's got to be a way.
- I can think of a way.
- I get it, kiddo.
You want to help people. Watch over 'em.
The best thing you
can do for Shayla...
- allow her to become a memory.
- No.
True courage is about
being honest with yourself.
Especially when it's difficult.
There is no plan where
both you and Shayla survive.
I can think of a way.
This new world that we are so
close to creating will never be.
And that new world, that is success.
Fsociety is success.
Look at what you accomplished
at Steel Mountain.
- That got us nowhere.
- You took them down.
You won that battle.
This... this is failure.
This is the old Elliot.
The one who turns to morphine,
to drugs when he feels weak.
A coward who can't face the truth,
even though it's staring
him right in the face.
(Elliot voice-over) There's
that sensation again.
Fight or flight.
Three lives at stake, including my own.
I, Elliot Alderson, am...
what?
[suspenseful music]
Tom Petty, Pink Floyd,
Van Halen? What's up, man?
You ain't got no Drake,
no Pitbull, no nothing?
Like, what's up? What the fuck?
- What's up, Rain Man?
- I'm ready to bust Vera out.
I can get into the network.
We need to go to the jail.
Now.
- She stays here.
- No, I'm not leaving you.
Don't worry,
he's in no position to
be giving out orders.
Let's go, girl.
(Elliot voice-over) Remember when the
panic would set in and we had a solution?
To be honest, I miss that.
Life is so much easier when you're numb.
- What's the plan, bitch boy?
- First Shayla, now Darlene.
- Yo, what the fuck?
- Elliot, what are you doing?
(Elliot voice-over) Like a hard
drive blasted by excessive voltage,
my mind is frayed.
Close to fried.
I can feel the static
running through my brain.
Serotonin receptors working overtime.
I need more time.
- Tonight, tonight, tonight.
- More time right now.
I'm working on our project as we speak,
so it's in your best interest
to keep talking with me.
(Elliot voice-over) At the
security desk, my cell phone
is running an undetectable
activated signal sniffer
that will locate any kind
of wireless signal in sight.
By the time I leave this building,
I'll own its network.
Good on you.
Brave, but stupid.
You showed your face, and
then I skip out tonight.
- Who do you think they're gonna finger?
- I'm opening every cell.
That way, they can't
trace it back to you or me.
Yeah, bro.
[laughs]
That's what I'm talking about.
Whoo!
[laughs]
I told you, didn't I?
- The universe got big plans for us, bro.
- Sit back down.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
When you get out, I realize
you're gonna have to split.
You won't be able to stay
in the tri-state area.
Oh, I love this.
Go on.
Wherever you go, you're gonna
need funding to keep surviving.
Which means your whole operation still
needs to be making you money.
- Come on, Elliot. Give it to me.
- I hacked Isaac's phone.
He had everything. Your crew,
shipments, the entire operation.
I took it all. I own your whole world.
♪ ♪
I need your word.
When this goes down, Shayla and I go free.
You leave us alone.
Forever.
If anyone tries to hurt us,
if I even see one of your guys
following me, I leak everything.
- You're saying this knowing...
- You can kill me anytime, yes.
That's why I coded the leak
to auto-send every 24 hours
unless I continuously disable it.
No one else has access.
If anything happens to me or Shayla,
your money gets deleted.
♪ ♪
(guard) Guns up, Vera, let's go.
Remember.
I'ma hug you.
[indistinct P.A. announcement]
[door buzzes]
[door opens, closes]
[doorbell rings]
- So what's your deal?
- I'm hear to see Terry Colby.
(Terry) Who is that, another damn reporter?
No comment. Do you understand?
Do I know you?
Get the hell away from my home.
Get away from my home.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
(Elliot voice-over) WPA2 Wi-Fi?
Shit.
Borderline unhackable.
Getting that handshake could take days.
The noose is tightening.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
[indistinct radio chatter]
The mobile feed on the cameras.
I don't need to hack WPA2
when there's dedicated 4G.
_
♪ ♪
- We're good.
- I can pull this off.
- Get in.
- Let's go, girl.
Nah, just him.
- Yo, Isaac, what you doing...
- Nah, bro, it's fine.
I just want to have a
private chat with him.
Come on, it's cool.
We don't have any time, man.
- I got to get to work.
- Get the fucking in the car.
♪ ♪
- Yo man, where you going, what you doing?
- (Isaac) All good, all good.
- Just gonna have a talk.
- Are you doing?
[car engine starts]
[tires peel]
[dark music]
♪ ♪
(Elliot) Why are you doing this?
I can free your brother.
- I figured it out.
- It just wasn't your day, bruh.
I hacked your whole operation.
- If you kill me...
- You don't get it.
Like I said, it just wasn't your day.
Stop.
(Elliot voice-over) I suppose
a bullet through the brain
is peaceful in its own right.
You don't want me to free Vera.
That's why you don't
care about the operation.
- I'd pick better last words.
- You're trying to kill him.
That's why Vera wants to leave tonight.
That's what's been bugging me about you.
You never wanted me to break him out.
Your best option for survival
is to kill him in prison,
because if you don't,
you're dead.
You're the reason Vera's
locked up right now,
and he knows it.
Doesn't matter anyway.
Vera was just gloating about how
he got in with the right crew,
how he got the jump on some men.
He's not worried, man.
- He's protected now.
- Bullshit.
(Elliot) That leaves
you with a zero-sum game.
If you don't get him out of jail,
he'll have you killed for failing.
Only way this works in your favor
is for you to kill him first,
and you can't do that
with him inside anymore.
Shut up, motherfucker.
- Shut the fuckup.
- Let me free him.
When I break Vera out tonight,
you do with your brother what you want.
That's the only outcome
where you got the possibility of living.
It's your best move.
What makes you think I still
won't kill you afterwards?
I don't.
I'm just playing my best move.
(Elliot) I need 30 to 40
seconds with the patrol car's
Bluetooth connection to
run the exploit on the PLC.
- (Isaac) And then?
- (Elliot) The plan executes at 9:49.
All the cell doors should open.
Hey, I wanted to ask you about something.
- Oh, yeah, what's that?
- You.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[typing]
[indistinct radio chatter]
(woman) Give me a call.
- We'll grab a drink, talk, whatever.
- (man) All right.
♪ ♪
(Elliot voice-over) The
exploit's on his laptop.
[indistinct radio chatter]
Now I need to force-feed
it into the jail's network.
_
- (woman) I like what I hear.
- _
- [indistinct radio chatter]
♪ ♪
- I paused the exploit.
- Drive.
Darlene's no longer part of the plan.
(man on radio) We got an alarm
going off, east-side exit.
- What in the hell?
- Tell you what.
We go out, we drink, we dance,
see where the night takes us.
You sure you want to make
- that choice right now?
- I only need to press one key
to run the exploit. Or, I can press
another and disable the entire plan.
I made my move.
You make yours.
Shit.
Please move back, miss.
- I got to get back ASAP.
- Whatever.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Look, I got to come back now.
My computer's on the fritz.
Let's go to the meet, DJ.
(Elliot voice-over) If I mis-typed
one command, hit one wrong key,
the cell doors won't open.
And we both know what that means.
Did I make a mistake?
No, I don't make mistakes.
One minute till Vera.
For all his insane, inhumane ideas,
he does understand the world.
The wild savagery of the world.
♪ ♪
[cocks gun]
- What you need your piece for, bro?
- Boy Wonder says
he's opening all the cells.
If some fool tries to rush us,
I want to be ready.
[door buzzes]
- (DJ) Hey, what the shit?
- Power surge caused by all the cell doors
opening at the same time.
- What about security? Sirens?
- The jail's network will show
all cells locked and closed.
Alarms are silent for two minutes.
[power whirring]
[glass breaking]
[men shouting]
[dogs barking]
[shouting and barking]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[gunshot]
[shouting]
(Vera) Yes. Yes.
This shit right here,
this shit tastes better
than any pussy I ever had.
Whoo! [laughs]
[shouting]
DJ, shoot the cocksucker.
My own brother.
That's what the universe asked of me.
To be my brother's keeper.
Like Cain after Abel,
I'll be a fugitive and
wanderer on the earth.
Brave fugitive.
Brave wanderer.
Look how you helped me.
That's the kind of bravery
I've been talking about.
But now...
now I want you to look at Isaac.
- Look.
- [Elliot groans]
[indistinct P.A. announcement]
Dead proof.
My operation is over.
So go on, crash it.
Burn it to the ground.
Doesn't matter.
- I'm gone.
- [siren blaring]
A spirit.
One with all the heavens.
All existence.
Shayla.
- Where is she?
- Keys, yo.
Told you you'd get her back, bro.
You just didn't realize she
was with you the whole time.
[siren wails]
[dark music]
♪ ♪
[inhales sharply]
[chokes]
[intense music]
♪ ♪
Synced and corrected by skoad
Resync by GoldenBeard
www.tvsubtitles.net