I will be the youngest executive
this company has ever seen.
All right, you know, I'll
take it if you leave us alone.
- Thank you.
- All right?
Check track two out.
- Well, track two.
- All right, man.
Why didn't you tell
me about the DAT file?
Worked at Evil Corp his whole life,
and out of the blue he got fired.
No one knew why. He had leukemia.
Made me swear to never tell anyone.
Finally, I got so worried, told my mom.
When he found out, he got pissed.
You ever think you deserved it?
I was eight years old...
You didn't commit to the
sacred pact you'd formed.
* *
My approach
within our business units
is to first invest in new technologies
and develop prototypes
in order to understand
the technology potential,
because despite the recent success
of our cyber security team,
our company currently still has
72 potential hacker vulnerabilities
in our primary and secon... oh, wait.
It's 73, you stupid piece of shit.
Again.
Our company currently still has
73 potential hacker vulnerabilities
in our primary and
secondary data centers.
Now is not the time to be encumbered
by the company's
tragic and shameful loss
of our chief Te...
Too formal, God damn it.
Warm it up. Don't be a cold robot.
Again.
Now is not the time to be encumbered
by the company's
tragic and shameful loss
of our chief technology officer.
We have to be swift in
naming the replacement CTO,
and, sir, I would like
to suggest it be me.
For the sake of our company,
that we make our decision today,
my promotion...
My internal promotion shows
not only our confidence
as a company, but strength
in our boldness to the public.
Thank you for your time.
You will be the next
CTO of this company.
Sure you don't want anything?
Pellegrino, tea?
Sir, thank you again for seeing me.
Tyrell, I'm gonna have
to reschedule this.
- Anwar, set up another time.
- Sir, it's just that I think...
I get it, I get it.
We'll get another meeting
on the books right away.
We've got a really good CTO candidate
the board is very excited about.
They're not ready to discuss it yet.
We'll loop you in.
Just give us a couple of weeks, hmm?
Uh, put Wellick back on the books.
Two weeks.
Oh, nice tie.
Let me guess.
Brioni?
Great taste, as always.
Be well.
I'll email your assistant the details.
If you could,
just email it to me directly.
This is too important for me to miss.
* *
Mr. Wellick, we're here.
You think I could have 300 this time?
Spoken like a true capitalist.
* *
Bad day at the office?
No ki...
Please, enough. No more.
Sync and corrections by: kDragon
Mr. Robot SO1E03
Original air date 07/08/2015
Most coders
think debugging software
is about fixing a mistake,
but that's bullshit.
Debugging's actually all
about finding the bug,
about understanding why the
bug was there to begin with,
about knowing that its
existence was no accident.
It came to you to deliver a message,
like an unconscious bubble
floating to the surface,
popping with a revelation
you've secretly known all along.
I don't know why I'm saying all of this.
Maybe it's because I'm
pumped up on whatever Sm... -
legal drug dealers like Eli Lilly
make money off nowadays.
But usually it's because
there's a sense it's coming.
A bug buzzing its way towards me
to gum up the works until
it forces me to make a call.
Kill me or embrace me.
Or maybe I'm just freaking
out because I never thought
I'd wake up to find these
two women staring back at me.
Are you awake?
I don't know.
What are you doing here?
We talked maybe a few hours ago
when I first got here.
You don't remember?
They said I was your emergency contact.
Um, right.
Um, you told them to
call your psychiatrist.
You can't leave until you talk to one.
So I'm gonna wait outside.
Hey.
Do you remember requesting
me from the staff?
You requested me because
the police said that...
I got jumped by a bunch of kids.
It's not the end of the world.
They wanted to do a full
drug panel, and you refused.
May I ask why?
Elliot, if we can't have
a conversation about this...
I've been taking morphine.
Why?
I don't have a good
enough reason to give you.
I wish I did, but I don't.
Maybe we should consider rehab.
I'm not a junkie.
Then you'll need to prove it to me.
Submit to a bimonthly
drug test voluntarily.
That's the only way that
I'll recommend your release.
Hospitals.
A heavily networked one like this
are almost too easy to hack.
This is William Highsmith.
He's not only the head
of the IT department here,
he is the IT department.
He's also an idiot,
not that I blame him because
the people that hired him
are also idiots.
The poor guy only gets a budget
of about 7,000 bucks a year,
and he's supposed to
protect their network
from people like me?
He never stood a chance.
He uses useless virus
scans, dated servers,
and security software
that runs on Windows 98.
It's one of the reasons
why I made this place
my primary care facility.
I can make my health records
look like every other
obedient zombie out there.
Okay.
You don't have to worry.
I'm not gonna do morphine again.
Hey, you got some matches?
Thank you.
* *
That's a nice breakfast.
Sorry. Credit card system is down.
Like I said,
the most difficult thing about debugging
isn't fixing the bug.
It's all about finding the bug.
For Evil Corp, Mr. Robot
found their bug in me.
I was the mistake that
led to all of this.
I have to ask you one thing.
Did you have something to
do with Vera getting busted?
Shit, Elliot.
You said you weren't gonna do anything.
He's on murder charges,
do you know that?
His whole crew bounced.
I mean, I don't know what
I'm gonna do for money now.
Just tell me, Elliot,
and don't lie.
Did you do something?
No.
Hmm.
Hey.
Are you okay?
I mean, with everything that happened...
I'm fine.
What happened to your door?
You're not supposed to be here, okay?
I changed the locks for a reason.
Mmm.
Interesting toy,
but you may want to spend
a little more scratch
if you actually want it to, you know,
work.
Check it.
Jessica Alba says she
wants to join Fsociety.
Jesus, what happened to your face?
What's going on?
Well, I am not the
princess of social graces,
but typically it goes something like,
- "Hi, this is Darlene".
- Stop.
You need to leave.
Babe, seriously, we have
a lot of shit to discuss,
so if you wouldn't mind...
Get out.
I suggest you get a grip.
What was she talking about?
I got to get to work.
Work? Are you serious?
You can't go to work.
You have to call in sick.
I have to go.
A bug is never just a mistake.
It represents something bigger.
An error of thinking.
- Sir! Sir! Sir!
- That makes you who you are.
Sir! You dropped your wallet.
- Thanks.
- Stop!
Stop! He stole my purse.
That was your wallet?
Yes, that was my wallet
you just gave him.
Stop!
He got into my
system, and he wants me
to put the CD on one of
the computers at work.
- Why does he want to do that?
- I don't know, Stella.
He didn't give me a full explanation.
So he's got naked pics of me?
Is that the only thing
you're seriously taking away
from this conversation?
Hey, babe.
- Hey.
- How was your run?
Strange.
Someone dropped their wallet,
and I picked it up to give
it to them, but then this...
Nothing strange about
that... just shows how good
of a person you are.
Always have been.
Almost to a fault.
What does that mean?
Just that you...
you're too good for the world.
That's probably why I love you.
I'm gonna hop in the shower.
I told you I can't talk.
You
have 100 hours precisely.
After that, everything
we own will be released.
____
It's not enough, just to focus
your attention on the logs.
We should also monitor
social media traffic
as well as IRC, Pastebin.
And set up scripts to keep going 24/7.
I mean, we might get lucky.
They might get sloppy,
make a mistake, you know...
This the world we live in.
People relying on each other's mistakes
to manipulate one another
and use one another,
even relate to one another.
A warm, messy circle of humanity.
Elliot.
I'm inviting you guys to dinner tonight.
Morton's notwithstanding,
I cook a mean steak.
What? Can't a boss invite his
favorite employees to dinner?
No, that's cool, but I got plans.
Can you guys give us a minute?
Yeah.
You want to tell me what's going on?
- Not really.
- Oh.
You're missing work, you
come in looking like that,
and you expect me not to ask questions?
Look, I don't know how
much you want me asking
about your personal life, but...
Not at all, actually.
I mean, I don't mean to be rude.
I was... I'm just being honest.
Mr. Robot may
have found Evil Corp's bug,
but he didn't find mine.
That's the only way to protect myself.
Never show them my source code.
Close myself off.
Create my cold, perfect maze
where no one can ever find me.
Elliot, I cannot believe you work here.
This place is a shithole.
Look, I thought I'd swing by,
take you to lunch.
Oh, that's nice.
I think she likes you, bud.
All right, fine, I'll take her,
but let the record show I was
trying to be a good wingman.
Oh, calm down. Shit.
I'm not that into redheads anyway.
The whole nation of
Ireland makes my dick soft.
Leave.
Darlene said we need to talk.
Leave now.
You're right. Probably
shouldn't talk here.
Let's go to that bar next door.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
I'm not going anywhere until you do,
so I can hang out here
and create a scene,
or you can give me five
minutes at the bar next or.
Either way, I'm gonna have fun.
Dealer's choice.
Mmm.
What? It's an Appletini.
I should kick your ass.
Mmm.
If that'll make us square,
you have my blessing.
Nah, man, I want nothing to do with you.
You're a maniac.
What can I get for you?
Uh, nothing.
You should probably order something.
- I'd recommend this...
- Fine.
I'll... I'll have an Appletini.
You should take it as a compliment, guy.
These things are goddamn delicious.
I get it.
Compliments make me uncomfortable too.
I find that hard to believe.
Yeah, who am I kidding?
I love compliments.
$12.
I really don't think you enjoyed that.
- I suggest sipping...
- Last chance.
What do you want?
I'm sorry for what I did.
I don't buy it.
More importantly, I don't give a shit.
I never wanted to hurt you.
People who get violent get that way
because they can't communicate.
Your dad,
I bet he felt shitty
for doing what he did.
I'm sure he wanted to apologize too.
Sometimes pushing your
kid away is just easier.
Don't stay mad at him too long, kiddo.
You're leaving?
That's what you want, isn't it?
What about your plan?
Plan?
You're the key to the whole thing.
Without you, there is no plan.
That's it?
It's over?
Expect me to believe that?
See you in another life.
Did you hear that?
I can't believe it.
Is it really happening?
Fsociety finally over.
The recent glitch in the
otherwise neat reality
I created over the years.
I'll never slip up like that again.
I'm gonna be more normal now.
Maybe Shayla could
even be my girlfriend.
I'll go see those stupid Marvel movies
with her. I'll join a gym.
I'll heart things on Instagram.
I'll drink vanilla lattes.
I'm gonna lead a
bug-free life from now on.
Anything to protect my perfect maze.
* *
Hey, Gideon.
Is that dinner still on for tonight?
Um, yeah. Sure.
Uh, you want to come?
Yeah.
Great.
Can I bring my girlfriend?
You have a girlfriend?
Well, I, uh, haven't asked her yet,
but I will.
Hopefully she'll say yes.
Uh, yeah. Sure.
Perfect.
Thanks.
* Steal my sunshine *
* My sunshine *
* If you steal my sunshine *
Was he drinking Starbucks?
Are you still trying to rip that CD?
Yeah, it's all... it's all scratched up.
Let's get out of here.
___
My boss invited me to a dinner party
at his place tonight.
I thought you could
come as my girlfriend.
What?
Are you actually asking me to
be your girlfriend right now?
Yeah.
Anyway, I need you.
I'm not good in social
situations like that.
There is something
seriously wrong with you.
I'm not gonna be used anymore.
Why don't you ask the girl
from this morning, okay?
She seems like she might
want to go to some stupid,
stuffy dinner party.
You don't actually know me.
All you know is that I'm the girl...
Of course I know Shayla.
I hacked her email as soon
as she moved in next door.
With a simple phishing scam,
I owned her password pretty easily.
I'm not talking about the
stuff you can find online.
I'm talking about the real me.
Tell me, then.
No. Forget it.
I want to know.
What is this?
I just put all the elements...
- It's beautiful.
- Together.
I've never seen this before.
- She must...
- Never posted online.
Um, I mean, a lot of them's not...
they're not done.
She's got her
own private maze too.
Took a lot of different pieces,
um, from different things,
like from my photographs
or drawings and...
Like, there's this one.
Um, it's really f... ing corny,
but, like, it has everything...
the kids and the...
Shayla's bug
was always elusive to me.
Maybe this was it.
Wanting normalcy but
stuck in the outer fringes,
not knowing how to participate.
Just like me.
Can I kiss you?
Next time, don't ask.
It's lame.
Bugs usually get a bad rap.
But sometimes...
Don't let me down, okay?
When a bug
finally makes itself known,
it can be exhilarating,
like you just unlocked something.
grand opportunity
waiting to be taken advantage of.
Mr. Wellick?
Hey.
What was your name again?
Anwar.
I didn't know you came
to places like this.
I don't.
What do you mean? You're here now.
I'm here because you are.
What? Sorry, I don't get it.
I think you're beautiful.
I want to take you home.
Wait, I thought you were married.
Because, after all,
a bug's only purpose,
it's only reason for existence
is to be a mistake that needs fixing,
to help you right a wrong.
And what feels better than that?
So, Elliot,
do you think you should introduce us?
Oh, um, Shayla, this
is Angela and Ollie.
You, uh, you look lovely this evening.
What up, guys?
You just get here?
Nice suit.
Thanks, dude.
- Shit.
- What is up with you?
You've been fidgeting all night.
Maybe we should try the doorbell again.
Hey, guys.
How long have you
been standing out here?
The doorbell is broken.
I should have warned you.
Come in. I'm Harry, by the way.
- Angela. Nice to meet you.
- Good to meet you.
- Always nice to put a face...
- Hey.
With an employee badge number, right?
Ollie, how long have
you guys been together?
- 2 and a half years.
- 2 years.
Okay.
Elliot, how long have you
and Shayla been together?
Well, uh, um,
J... just today.
* Memories passed *
* So free and easy *
* First and last... *
Okay, enough grilling of the guests.
Let's check on the real grill, shall we?
Elliot, I could use your help.
So I have a confession.
I had the SYS admins at
the data center in Dulles
check that server again.
Gideon, what did you do?
Of course there was nothing.
I have no idea what there was
to even be suspicious about.
I mean, what possible
motivation would you have
to do anything? I guess
I was just being...
Gideon has to let this go.
If he comes near this hornet's nest,
I'm not sure I can save him from it.
I have to kill any suspicion left.
You've been nothing but
a hard worker for Allsafe,
so I apologize.
After the conversation on the plane,
I knew what was at
stake... the whole company.
I was worried that the DAT file I found
wasn't the right one.
I just didn't
want to get your hopes
up in case I was wrong.
That's why I didn't tell
you before the meeting.
Shit.
I'm gonna have to let
him hug me, aren't I?
You're such a brilliant
engineer, Elliot,
and you should never doubt your skills
no matter how much
pressure I put on you.
And you certainly don't have
to keep anything from me.
I care about you.
From the Mixed-up Files
of Basil E. Frankweiler.
That's where I got the idea, remember?
I wanted to be Claudia Kincaid so bad.
Even her name was cool.
Remember we thought we
were going to The Met,
somehow we ended up at
The Queens Museum instead?
No Google Maps back then.
I loved running away with you.
Somehow when you're eight,
running away can be fun.
The normal life.
Smiles, dinner parties,
childhood stories.
I could get used to this,
maybe even like it.
What's wrong?
Corp's
hacking scandal continues
with the release of these latest emails.
Information stemming from
the latest dump reveals
that Terry Colby was one of
three high-level executives
involved in the cover-up
of the widely publicized
Washington Township toxic waste scandal.
If these reports are true,
Colby may be facing more indictments.
In the ensuing 24 months
after the alleged toxic
waste leak in 1993,
26 employees died from
similar types of leukemia.
Evil Corp, however, managed
to get the class-action lawsuit
filed against it by the
surviving victims dismissed,
claiming there was no
direct evidence linking
their factories to the diagnoses.
Now these emails indicate
that Colby was in fact aware
of the dangerous levels of toxicity
and kept it a secret as it
"would not be cost-effective
to retool the current systems
in place even if there
are potential lawsuits".
Mr. Colby was unavailable
for comment, but his lawyer...
My perfect maze
crumbling before my eyes.
Data dump are
further proof Colby was set up,
but they didn't indicate by whom.
There's nothing to hide behind.
I didn't think it
existed, but there it was.
Is.
Mr. Robot finally found my bug.
Linking the waste
levels in Washington Township
to the victims' illnesses.
Legal analysts support the claim
that there is not enough evidence...
What's going on?
That's how my mom,
um, and Elliot's dad...
- I have to go.
- Wait, wait.
- Let me come with you.
- No, I'd rather you didn't.
Evidence in the Washington
Township scandal.
Terry Colby remains under investigation
for his alleged involvement with the...
Dismissed
because there was no evidence
linking the waste levels
in Washington Township...
Evil Corp...
Don't look so sad.
He did this to himself.
He gave in. He was a coward.
He was weak and pathetic.
And in the end, that's
what killed your father.
Why are you crying?
Don't ask so many questions.
I miss him.
There's no point to that.
But I do.
Then you're just as weak as him.
You're not sad?
Why should I be?
It's a beautiful night.
The weather is nice,
and I'm enjoying my cigarette.
The bug forces
the software to adapt,
evolve into something new because of it.
Work around it or work through it.
No matter what, it changes.
It becomes something new.
The next version.
The inevitable upgrade.
You're a strange creature.
I'm just a businessman.
And that's about as
clean as I'm gonna get it.
You have to do the rest in the shower.
I don't mind being a little dirty.
I do.
You should join me.
Yeah, I'll be there in a minute.
Hey.
I'm sorry that I ran off like that.
Did you talk to him?
Nope. He wasn't home.
Well, I'm here.
I want to talk to you about everything,
just not tonight, okay?
So you talked to him,
but not with you boyfriend?
It's different, Ollie.
Both of our parents died because...
That's how we know each other.
I really don't want to
talk about this right now.
What if I do?
What if you do what?
Want to talk.
About...
something.
What the hell are you talking about?
I have to tell you something.
I don't know why you're
putting yourself through this.
You don't have to keep looking at it.
All right? It meant nothing.
Okay, I know I sound
like a broken record,
but I love you, and
I want to be with you.
Stop speaking.
Just tell me what you need
in order for me to fix
this, and I'll do it.
We need to break up.
Angela, come on.
What choice did you give me, Ollie?
Look, I know I have a problem.
I'm not denying that.
Well, maybe my problem is
I can't be with a guy with your problem.
Where's the CD?
It's in my... in my bag. Why?
He has my bank account, Ollie.
- And my dad's bank account.
- How did they...
Our accounts are linked
because of my student loans.
I used your laptop to access it.
He has my dad's social security,
his credit card numbers, everything.
Okay.
Okay, that is bad,
but I'm sure the cops
will figure out a way...
If we don't do what this guy says
and we go to the cops,
then he's just going to sell
our information to the highest bidder,
and me and my dad are
completely screwed.
Do you have any idea how difficult it is
to come back from massive
identity theft like this?
What are you saying?
Angela, are you crazy?
No, we cannot just
infect Allsafe's network
because of this.
I'll lose my job.
And there it is.
You'll lose your job too,
if that matters.
Besides, even if we put the CD in,
who says this guy won't
just do all this anyway?
Hey.
Hey, hey, come here.
Look at me.
We are going to figure this out.
Okay?
You're right. You're right.
I'm sorry.
I'm just scared.
I don't want to break up with you.
I'm sorry that I said that.
Oh.
I love you so much.
This is admin, Dulles.
Yeah, hi, this is Gideon
Goddard at Allsafe Security.
I need to talk to Sean Skyler
about server CS30 again.
Hold please. I'll transfer you.
* *
___
Here's the plan.
www.tvsubtitles.net