So, what do we got?
Terry Colby was involved in the cover-up
of the Washington Township
toxic waste scandal.
What do we need to prove our case?
Someone who was there
when the decision was made
to falsify chemical waste intel.
Get the hell away from my
home. Get away from my home!
Elliot, what is going on with you?
I cannot help you if
you keep me in the dark.
We got problems.
The Dark Army is bailing.
It's not over.
We'll find a way, just not tonight.
How do you not blow your
brains out married to him?
You want to watch me piss too?
- Scott, a misunderstanding...
- Happy to pull my dick out for you.
Elliot!
- Where is she?
- I told you you'd get her back, bro.
Shit!
Open up!
I'm bleeding all over the hallway!
It's a life-or-death
situation out here!
Look, I know you're in
there. I just saw you go in.
Open up!
I'm looking...
Well, are you just gonna stand there?
Get me a glass of water, dummy.
Can I use this? Thanks.
My niece gave him to me.
I haven't even named him yet. God.
Do you know the pressure
of an ecstatic six-year-old?
I mean, I kill that thing,
and her whole world collapses.
I like what you did with the place.
Hmm.
Yeah, nice setup. Still
like mine better though.
Yo, let me know if you
want a top-shelf hookup.
Actually, now that I have you...
will you help me move
a dresser... Mr. Muscles?
Okay, come on. Just come on.
Man 'N' Van is getting way too legit.
They used to just be, like, drummers
with their mom's Honda Odysseys.
Now it's an actual company in Queens.
I mean, the guys are literally men in vans.
I'd buy morphine from you,
if you could also get me Suboxone.
Well, it's pretty much
impossible to get Suboxone.
My supplier doesn't have it.
I saw this song live once. It was so rad.
Don't you just love hearing
your favorite songs in person,
like, half deaf from the speakers,
- everyone going nuts around you?
- No.
Direct. I respect that.
I just hate concerts.
Lots of people.
- You don't like people, huh?
- Not most of them, no.
Okay.
Well, so by that rationale, if you were
to really like one person, it'd be, like,
considered an aberration or an abnormality
- or special, even.
- I guess.
Well, I aim for special,
so challenge accepted.
I wish we already knew each other.
Would make this feel less awkward.
- You really feel awkward right now?
- Yeah.
Well, then I wish we
knew each other too then.
Oh, yikes.
I, um, I'm late. Meeting
the girls for drinks.
Oh, um, I'm Shayla.
Elliot.
You know, I do know of
a guy who sells Suboxone.
He's supposed to be
a fucking psychopath,
but if you want, I can call him.
You might be worth a psychopath.
I don't know. Maybe.
Oh, and keep the fish, you filthy animal.
- Synced and corrected by skoad -
www.addic7ed.com
Sorry I
haven't talked to you in a while.
I mean, it's only been
a month, which I guess
in the grand scheme of
things isn't that long.
Isn't our life like a blip
in the cosmic calender or something?
So that's Shayla.
A blip.
Not even.
Here one blip, gone the next.
Makes me hate myself that
I've already gotten used to
the idea of her not being here.
In a year, I'll maybe think about her
every once in a while.
Then she'll become an
anecdote, a thing to say.
"I knew a girl that died,"
with the added bonus of,
"She died because of me."
- Maybe I should hate myself.
- Here are the last two forms.
She's getting rid of me,
in case you're still
trying to figure that out.
- Once I...
- Sign on the bottom.
Then I'll deliver it to the court,
and in two weeks' time, you'll receive
an official release from the mandate.
That second form means
that we've been sitting
- in this room for a year.
- Over 52 hours
of Krista's voice
bouncing around this room.
She thinks she's a
wasted echo. Maybe she is.
I wonder how much time I've spent
- not listening to her in here.
- I'm worried about you, Elliot.
I really want you to keep coming here.
We've got a lot more work to do.
She wants more from me
but she doesn't believe in me.
I tried because I believe
some part inside of you
- wants to do this right.
- You?
Are you on her side?
You should clean your sockets.
Sounds too good to be true, but I'll bite.
- What's the ask?
- Given my client has information
that could help your client's case,
we want the meeting restricted
to her, Colby, and myself,
- and we want it conducted off-record.
- Antara, come on.
- My client won't accept your presence.
- Our client pays for ours.
Then you're duty-bound to present him
with any legitimate offer
of beneficial evidence.
Of course.
Give us something truly
legitimate and beneficial.
You won't even tell us what
the hell your client has.
Seth, we've been sitting on opposite sides
of the negotiating table for two decades.
I'm not some joker come out of the woodwork
trying to scam Colby for millions.
I'm giving him the only
glimmer of hope he's had.
We'll pass along your
offer. Thanks for your time.
Lloyd said you wanted to see me.
Look, I appreciate your
commitment to this job.
I really do.
But I don't see how you've plowed through
these last few weeks, so I
want to offer you some time off.
- Just some time to...
- I don't need time off.
I'm good.
Uh... uh, one more thing.
Look,
I'm so sorry she was taken away, Elliot,
but don't let her death
close you off entirely.
Find someone you can be
your honest self with, okay?
I remember when
I was a kid, I got into web design
by ripping off sites I liked.
All you had to do was
view source on your browser
and there it was, the code.
You could copy-paste
it, modify it a little,
put your name on it, and
like that, it was your site.
View source.
What if we had that for people?
Would people really want to see?
- _
_
Find someone to be your honest self with?
Bullshit.
Really good advice. Thanks.
I quote, "The U.S.
contingent of the hacker group Fsociety
"has remained quiet since
the upheaval inflicted
"upon the world's largest
multinational conglomerate.
"Secretary of Homeland Security Jeh Johnson
"released a statement today stating that,
"'These groups lack the
resources and knowledge
of the U.S cell to
successfully mount an attack.'"
End quote.
- Yeah, so?
- We gotta get the Dark Army back.
Dude, I've been trying.
How many times do you want me to hack him?
Do you know how hard hacking a hacker is?
- Cisco switches OSes, like, all the time.
- Darlene, we need one meeting.
Yeah, well, I've been using Cisco's handle
to send requests for the past month.
I got nothing.
He's slower than me, but not by much.
If we can talk to
whiterose directly...
Whiterose? Whiterose?
Really?
Okay, if the guy even exists,
and that's a big if, no way
he's meeting you face-to-face.
For all we know...
this dude's whiterose.
Excuse me!
Are you whiterose?
A likely story.
'Sides, the tape backups already shipped
to all the new Steel Mountain facilities,
and we still haven't
found a way around that.
- I got a plan in motion.
- And God's laughing.
This
is all I have left of her.
I will miss her.
I need to wipe again.
So if you scroll to the next page,
you'll see the summary of capital budgets
- or purchasing and operations.
- We get it. The goddamn earning reports
- are gonna look good come Monday.
- Our aim is to facilitate bill payment
and heighten financial security,
so that's an extra 2%.
You know, if we hadn't
turned our profits around,
- I was gonna leave.
- No way.
Where? Don't tell me Apple.
- Google.
- Don't buy it.
I got a blow job from the hiring executive
on the Googleplex volleyball court.
Oh, she was hot.
Had a Marissa Mayer thing going on too.
Hot execs started as hot assistants
who fucked their way to the top
twice as fast as the rest of us.
You know something screwed up?
I heard that, some
assistants, they're going gay
- to move up the ladder.
- I'll do you one better.
There's a special handful
of pathetically desperate
execs going cock jockey.
No. Oh, my God!
Hey, Dwight, I meant to
ask. How are your children?
Hell if I know. Sent 'em off to Lawrence.
I think Julia likes art.
- Oh, well. Can't win 'em all.
- Lawrence?
You'll never be able
to afford that tuition on unemployment.
- Sorry?
- You're fired!
You two as well.
I'm making sure you all receive
the minimum severance packages.
Mr. Wellick, I don't understand.
What did we do?
Nothing.
- After...
- You said you would update me.
I needed to discuss our situation
with the state's attorney.
- Thanks for coming in, Roy.
- Yeah.
I think you should have a seat.
Colby's lawyers called 30 minutes ago.
They wanted a promise of total
immunity before the meeting,
which I obtained from the man you just met.
So, yes, Colby agreed...
with a caveat.
I can't be in the room.
You have to go in alone.
Look, you made a ballsy move...
but you doing what
you're about to do...
entering the home of a very powerful man
with a lot at stake and
asking him for something...
that's always a dangerous proposition.
So one last time...
are you sure you want to do this?
Shit, man.
Thought you was one of them high schoolers
stole my mom's chaise lounge.
As heartbreaking as it is to hear that,
you're gonna have to put that off.
Getting everybody back together.
- Come on.
- No, man, not this time.
I'm out.
You can't be out. We need you.
Look, man, I got a new set of
people depending on me, okay?
Clients out the wazoo.
So, you know, I mean, good luck,
and tell the kids I said hi.
- What is this? What are you doing here?
- Well, I figured out how to insert
THC's genetic information
code into yeast cells.
Tripled my earning speed.
Plants need weeks to
develop. Microbes need days.
So, what, you got a Bath and Body Works
- bottling facility in your backyard?
- Try it.
The THC level is borderline in that blend,
and the lavender doesn't
mess with the high.
You just smooth it on your skin.
So you're rejecting a revolution
in favor of aroma profiles?
What a waste of potential.
Look, man, I know I got a good brain.
Besides...
what was our little
project in the end, anyway?
Wasted shit, if you ask me.
Well, now you're borderline pissing me off.
Is that a fact?
And what exactly are you gonna do
- if I decide to cross that border?
- Look at my face, Romero.
You and I both know I'm crazy.
Not the cute kind either.
I'm talking crazy crazy!
You lost touch.
You forgot the feeling of spilling blood
on the battlefield by winning the fight.
I didn't want to hurt you, Romero.
I love you, man.
I just wanted you to come
back to the arcade with me
so we could change the world together.
I am clearly too crazy
for you to say no to.
Bang!
- Look on your face is priceless!
- Goddamn lunatic.
You gave me your word
when we started this thing
that you'd finish it.
I gave you my word what
I'd do if you didn't.
See you back at the arcade.
Good. I see the girl got you tea.
Well, let's get started.
How much do you want?
Write your number.
You can ask me anything you want,
but I promise you, at the end of the day,
money will always be better
than what you're looking for.
Mr. Colby, did you attend
the executive board meetings during 1993?
Were you in the room
when the decision was made
to ignore the treatment of hazardous waste
in Washington Township?
I have information which can help you...
if you answer my question.
I don't know what you're talking about.
If you agree to testify
against the executives
who covered up the illegal
dumping of epoxy resin waste,
I will testify that I
broke chain of custody
with the dat file central to your case.
You're that hot little thing
that came by here a month ago.
The girl from Allsafe.
I remember, yeah.
Okay... I'm gonna answer your question.
But here's what I need from you first.
So I'm gonna pull down my pants,
and then I'm gonna need you to
take that pouty mouth of yours
and swallow up my balls.
Now, they're big and hairy,
especially the left one,
so you're really gonna
have to, I don't know,
squish 'em up to get 'em inside there.
You're probably gonna have
to do one cheek at a time.
But then, once they're
all warm and snug in there,
I want you to repeat your question to me
as clearly as you can.
Then, and only then,
am I willing to answer.
What do you say?
If you don't take this deal...
you'll become like me.
Sure, maybe you'll live in this house...
maybe you'll have money,
but even if your expensive
lawyers find a way
to get you off, people will
still think that you're guilty.
Losing everyone's respect...
The respect of people you know
and the people you don't...
it's a shitty feeling.
Trust me.
I'll have "the girl" let me out.
Flipper. Is she microchipped?
Okay, very good.
Housekeeping done.
Now onto the real business.
- Has your dog ever eaten trash before?
- No. I mean, not that I remember.
Well, lucky for your bank account,
the piece is small
enough to pass on its own.
Unfortunately, though, it's large enough
to send her puking all over your apartment.
So I would crate her for
a few days and monitor her.
She won't know what you're
doing is good for her.
What the hell did you do?
You were right. I was
only trying to prove...
Colby's lawyers
just called. He wants to talk.
Get back there.
It's a little early in the
morning to be nerding out,
- don't you think?
- How long?
- Hmm?
- I knew if I asked you that...
- How long?
- Couple weeks.
And you had the balls to ask
for whiterose with my shit?
It's like you want to get us both killed.
What happened? He responded?
You know, you didn't have to make me look
like a shitty foot soldier.
- Nobody would ever even know...
- You got root on my box and found the IP,
then you joined their
channel with my handle.
We're so done.
I don't want to see you again.
But you fools actually got your wish.
I don't know why,
but the meeting's actually gonna be on.
I'd tell you to be careful, but I know
that's the last thing you're gonna be.
My lawyers are looking over the paperwork.
- Does that mean that...
- Exactly what I said.
I asked you back here to make
sure that you can pull off
your testimony, make sure that this
chain of custody story
of yours is straight.
- I can't afford any trips.
- I'm not going to trip.
So, what...
what's in this for you, anyway?
I know you hate me.
So, what, you're gonna
just let me off Scot-free?
- What do you get out of this?
- Earlier, I asked you a question.
You never answered it.
If I'm agreeing to testify
in your case, then, yes,
you know, I attended several meetings.
Tell me about the one when
they decided to ignore the leak.
I'm not sure what you're asking.
What was the meeting like
when you decided this?
I get it.
You want to know, like, what was it like?
Like, um, did we all have
cigars and laugh hysterically
as we signed the evil documents?
Is that what you pictured?
Well, I'm sorry, hon.
See, the world doesn't work like that.
Tell me. Tell me how it works.
Uh, Jesus, um... all right, all right.
Let's see. January, '93.
Well, my secretary then was Elaine.
So Elaine brought us a
platter of shrimp cocktail
to tide us to dinner, which pissed us off
because we just had a
platter at the holiday party.
Jim opened the bar.
Now Jim was a real piece of work.
I mean, half pansy, half mafia.
First sign of a tight
decision, he'd be chain smoking
down a river of scotch.
Uh...
you know, it rained.
It rained. I remember that, yeah.
So...
you were drunk, eating shrimp cocktail,
and it was raining when you
decided my mother would die?
That's why.
So people like you won't keep
sitting in rooms together.
Did any of it ever give you or anyone pause
- when you made those decisions?
- Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
But, um...
then you go home, and,
uh, and you have dinner,
you know, and you
wake up the next morning.
Here's to a man who has a
bright future at our company,
a man you all know,
a man who is going to change
this company for the good,
a man smart enough to marry
a woman every bit his equal...
Our new Chief Technology
Officer, Scott Knowles.
- Here, here!
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Thank you, Phillip.
- Welcome.
- Thank you very much.
- Here we go.
- It's great to be here.
- And we're off.
- Thanks, Phillip.
- You're very welcome.
- Congratulations, darling.
- Thank you, thank you.
- I'll leave you to it, okay?
- Don't break a sweat.
- Oh, here, come, say hello.
- Hey, Joe, how are you?
_
Thank you.
- Tyrell, nice to see you.
- Is it?
I hear you shared our
moment with your husband.
Oh, come on.
That was over a month ago.
Don't tell me you're still sore.
Hmm, I sense some defeat.
Well, I considered myself, at
the very least, reprimanded.
How disappointing.
One tiny curveball and you gave up.
- Miss.
- Thank you.
Should have known that
you were nothing more
than a bold entrance.
Are you saying you don't
crave a bold entrance
every time, over and over, sustained?
- Meet me tonight.
- I'm a little busy.
- Come to my office now.
- Are you really asking me that?
I don't recall phrasing
it as a question, no.
Fine, then I just won't show up.
Then the roof.
Take the back stairwell.
The cameras have been out since March.
No one will know.
Well, you just made a long day longer.
I know that Allsafe will have to fire me,
but testifying was the right thing to do.
I have worked my ass
off to take care of you
and of every person in this company.
- Do you know what that means?
- You've been a great boss, Gideon...
See, once this confession goes public,
no one will want to do business with us.
The company will go under.
I couldn't let Colby take the fall
- for something that I did.
- Oh, come on!
You and I both know you
didn't break chain of custody.
- I did and I feel terrible...
- Angela! Please! Stop lying.
You do this... all these people go down,
all their families that rely
on what this company provides for them.
So this is where the rabbit hole leads?
Got to be honest,
I half-expected you not to show up.
And I half-expected
you to be a tattletale.
So you are sore.
Oh, come on. You intrigued me.
I intrigued back.
- Can't we just be more straightforward?
- Oh, that's no fun, but if you insist,
I just came up here to
see if you were really
as gullible as you seem.
My husband's downstairs
getting the job that you want,
and you're up here trying to fuck me.
Now whether that's you
being straightforward
or a game, either way,
- it's played pretty poorly, if you ask me.
- Hmm. Again, I asked no question.
All I can tell you is you need this
'cause you're dissatisfied.
Scott plans on firing you,
and you are clinging on
to any chance you can get.
You seem desperate.
Hey... hey!
What do you... get off of me!
Stop!
We connected with whiterose.
The plan is back on.
I could bullshit you, tell
you you're the only person
who can fill the exact
void we have at Fsociety.
The truth is, I need
this group back together.
Have you ever considered which part
of our scheme motivates you?
When the Dark Army bailed, you didn't care
if pushing a button would
bring an economic revolution.
You want momentary anarchy.
The others?
Mobley likes palling around.
Romero wants a whiff of fame.
Those reasons depress me.
- What's the part you want?
- You don't care.
My parents were born in Iran.
They came here like everybody else,
for freedom,
but my dad works 60-hour weeks
to determine tax loopholes
for a millionaire art dealer.
My mom, she ran up loans into five digits
to get an online degree.
They won't shut up about
how great America is.
But they're gonna die in debt doing things
they never wanted to do.
There are how many billion
- people in this world?
- 7.3.
Somehow you and I landed together...
doing something impossible
if we were alone,
not to mention at the
right point in history
with the right resources.
We have what we've worked for
right there for the taking.
We just need each other
to see this through.
You come any closer, I'm calling the cops.
Hi, operator. I'd like
to report an emergency.
I placed a malicious
CD in my work computer,
and now this guy at the
gym is saying hi to me.
- I'm going home.
- I need you to do something for me.
Call the girl who wants
to be involved, okay?
Her name is Angela Moss.
- Let me give you her phone number.
- Listen, pussy.
If you don't do what I say,
then the giant shit storm
that rains turds later
will leave a trail of clouds in
the sky spelling out your name.
Elliot?
- I wasn't expecting you.
- I'm here for my appointment.
Well, you can slip in
before my first patient.
- You told me I should tell you the truth.
- Yes.
Everything I say will still
be protected and confidential?
I've been lying to you.
I don't take my pills.
But you don't either.
Your refill frequency
for Ativan doesn't match
your prescription divided by the dosage.
This morning...
you bought a tall hazelnut latte.
Paid for it on your Evil Corp card.
By text, you justified the
indulgence to your sister
because Evil Corp gives you double rewards.
But those points only
accumulate on travel expenses.
You're not good with money.
On paper, your Thursday
2:00, Marilyn O'Brien,
is your doppelganger.
I think you're encouraging her
to leave her husband...
because you're tired of being dumped.
You like porn, especially anal.
Whether you like it yourself, I don't know.
That's not relevant to me.
You've told your best friend Jennifer
that you wish your mom would die.
I sometimes watch you on your webcam.
You cry sometimes...
just like me.
Because you're lonely.
I don't just hack you, Krista.
I hack everyone...
my friends, coworkers.
But I've helped a lot of people.
I want...
a way out of loneliness...
just like you.
Is that what you wanted to hear?
- Synced and corrected by skoad -
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net